Proven skills in increasing customer engagement and business visibility in online searches through successful SEO an SMO approaches.

Experienced in developing marketing initiatives, increasing business success and boost sales. Excellent analytical, organizational and decision-making abilities.

Work History

2021-08 current

SEO Executive/ Social Media Management

Intelus, Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Approaching niche related websites for backlinks.
- Negotiating for price with website owners.
- Handling Company's social media account.
- Making monthly social media calendar.
- Writing product reviews.
- Approaching Influencers for company's guest article for free.

2019-01 – 2021-04

Digital Marketer/ Project Manager

Finding PI, Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Helped clients develop website portals and social media pages to promote businesses.
- Produced and submitted weekly reports outlining progress against KPI objectives.
- Built, implemented and updated effective SEO strategies.
- Wrote off-site SEO content such as press releases, guest blog posts and informational articles.
- Communicated marketing teams' plans and accomplishments to verify alignment with senior management objectives.
- Created effective messaging using language, graphics and marketing collateral.
- Coordinated art and graphics creation for effective merchandising.
- Directed successful SEO and link-building campaign to increase website's credibility and drive traffic.
- Directed successful search engine marketing campaign that used solid linking, technical and

Romario Drazon

Digital Marketer

Personal Info

Address

Flat no. 402, Sai Residency, Ujjwal Nagar, Zingabai Takli, Nagpur, Maharashtra, 440030

Phone

770-960-6860, 899-935-9293

E-mail

romario.drazon@gmail.com

Skills

Blogging

Search engine optimization

Social media

Google Ads knowledge

Google Analytics understanding

Marketing strategies

Keyword optimization

Ad development

WordPress knowledge

keyword research tactics.

- Developed and managed communications strategies, plans and budgets.
- Analyzed third-party data and investigated new growth opportunities.
- Coached management on communication tactics with staff and customers regarding organization changes.
- Coordinated trade shows, media buying and planning, sales promotions and direct mail campaigns.
- Developed and deepened relationships with key customers by closely monitoring projects, providing information and resolving concerns.
- Prepared and gave presentations to clients and other project stakeholders.

2017-07 -2018-06

Area Marketer

Libra Tele Communication, Nagpur, Maharastra

- Devoted special emphasis to punctuality and worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- Performed various administrative functions, including filing paperwork, delivering mail, sorting mail.
- Maintain daily sales report. Accomplish weekly target.
- Report DSR to Manager.

2016-03 -2017-05

Back Office & HR

Elite Associate Group, Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Produced accurate office files, updated spreadsheets and crafted presentations to support executives and boost team efficiency.
- Responded to emails and other correspondence to facilitate communication and enhance business processes.
- Produce monthly invoices, reports and other deliverables.
- Greeted arriving visitors, determined nature and purpose of visit and directed individuals to appropriate destinations.

FindingPi Projects

simplydesi.in findingpi.com shreyastechnosoft.com omkarrashtradev.com saharsh.co mahasupport.com Publicreleases.com Communicate and, explain technical functions of mobile devices and guide product selection to the team.

2016-03 - Customer Executive

2017-05

2015-02

PAMA TeleTech PVT. LTD., Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Met all customer call guidelines including service levels, handle time and productivity.
- Maintain Daily Sales Report
- Performed data entry with [Software] to record call notes, suggestions and questions.
- Cold-called leads and closed, sales with in a Timeframe.

2013-01 - Back Office And Accountant

Centre Of Education, Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Completed daily accounting tasks including tracking funds, preparing deposits and reconciling accounts.
- Produced accurate office files, updated spreadsheets and crafted presentations to support executives and boost team efficiency.
- Notifying to sales department for pending payments.

Education

2009-08 - Bachelor of Science: Science Education

2012-06 CMJ University

Certifications

2018-08 Digital Marketing

MS-CIT

MS-OFFICE